Guide to the Leo Bogart Papers, 1912-2010 and undated RL.10146
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Series, 1914-2005 and undated, 84 boxes
  - Writings and Speeches Subseries, 1943-2004 and undated
    - Writings (Box 64)
      - Articles
        - 1994 Sept.-Oct., Consumer Games (Box 72)
        - 1994 Nov., Newspapers in the New Media World (Box 72)
        - 1994 Dec., The Dallas Model (Box 72)
        - 1994 Dec., Navigating the New Media (Box 72)
        - 1994, The American Media System and Its Commercial Culture (Box 72)
        - circa Jan. 1995, How Often is Enough? (Box 72)
        - 1995 Feb., Is There an Optimum Frequency in Advertising? (Box 72)
        - 1995 July-Aug., Three Views of Advertising: A Review Essay (Box 72)
        - 1996 Apr., The City and the Media in the Digital Age (Box 72)
        - Spring 1996, Highway to the Stars or Road to Nowhere? (Box 72)
        - Sept. 1996, Newspapers in the Era of Electronic News (Box 72)
        - 1996 Winter, Newspapers' Fate Tied to Revival of Cities (Box 72)
        - 1996 Dec., The New Media: Reporting or Journalism? (Box 72)
        - 1996, A Cidade e a Mídia na Era Digital (Box 72)
        - circa 1996, What Does It All Mean? (Box 72)
        - 1998 May-June, Politics, Polls, and Poltergeists (Box 72)
        - 1998 July-Aug., What Editors Should Know About Polls (Box 72)
        - 1998, Media Mergers and the Future of Books (Box 72)
        - 1998, Should the V-Chip Fall Where it May? (Box 72)
        - 1999 Spring, Newspapers (Box 72)
        - 1999 Summer, Max Ralis, 1916-1999 (Box 72)
        - 2000 Spring, review of Sparks of Liberty: An Insider's Memoir of Radio Liberty by Gene Sosin (Box 72)
        - 2000 Summer, Church and State (Box 72)
        - 2000 Sept.-Oct., Buying Services and the Media Marketplace (Box 72)
        - 2003 Summer, Reconstructing Past Social Moods from Paintings: The Eye of the Beheld, 1 of 3 folders (Box 72)
        - 2003 Summer, Reconstructing Past Social Moods from Paintings: The Eye of the Beheld (continued), 2-3 of 3 folders (Box 73)
        - 2004 Fall, Irving Crespi, 1926-2004 (Box 73)
        - 2004 Winter, Reflections on Content Quality in Newspapers (Box 73)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1953-2002 (Box 73)
      - Books (Box 74)
        - 1956, The Age of Television
          - Background materials, 1955-1957 and undated, 2 folders (Box 74)
          - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 74)
          - Dust jacket, 1956 (Box 74)
          - Materials for revisions, 1971-1979 and undated (Box 74)
          - Reviews, 1956-1958 (Box 74)
        - 1967, Strategy in Advertising
          - Anecdotes, 1965 (Box 74)
          - Correspondence, 1964-1982, 3 folders (Box 74)
          - Dust jackets, 1967 (Box 74)
          - Foreign rights, 1970-1975 (Box 74)
          - Paperback book, 1967 (Box 74)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1967-1971 (Box 75)
        - 1969, Current Controversies in Marketing Research
          - Correspondence, 1965-1985 (Box 75)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 75)
        - 1969, Social Research and the Desegregation of the U.S. Army
          - Background materials, 1967 and undated (Box 75)
          - Correspondence, 1951-1983, 2 folders (Box 75)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1970 (Box 75)
        - 1972, The Age of Television, 3rd edition
          - Background materials, 1955-1971 and undated (Box 75)
          - Correspondence, 1969-1983 (Box 75)
          - Materials for revisions, 1972-1974 and undated (Box 75)
          - Permissions requests, 1971-1972 (Box 75)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1972 (Box 75)
        - 1972, Silent Politics: Polls and the Awareness of Public Opinion (Box 76)
          - Background materials, 1969-1973 and undated, 5 folders (Box 76)
          - Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 76)
          - Permissions requests, 1971 (Box 76)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1972 (Box 76)
        - 1976, Premises for Propaganda: The United States Information Agency's Operating Assumptions in the Cold War
          - Against Dismembering USIA editorial, 1975 (Box 76)
          - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 76)
          - Dust jackets, 1976 (Box 76)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 76)
          - United States Information Agency (USIA) operating assumptions study materials (Box 77)
            - Background materials, 1953-1954 (Box 77)
            - Correspondence, 1953-1970 (Box 77)
            - International Information Administration Subcommittee reports, 1953 (Box 77)
            - Operating assumptions study materials, 1953-1962 (Box 77)
            - Research on the use of media in the Department of State's Overseas Information Program, 1951-1953 (Box 77)
            - Seminar on Communication Problems materials, 1968-1969 (Box 77)
            - A Study of the Operating Assumptions of the United States Information Agency, volumes 1-5, 1954
              - Summary, 1954 (Box 77)
              - Volumes 1-2, 1954, 2 folders (Box 77)
              - Volumes 3-5, 1954, 4 folders (Box 78)
            - USIA articles, 1968-1975 (Box 78)
            - USIA task force materials, 1960-1961 (Box 78)
        - 1981, Press and Public: Who Reads What, When, Where and Why in American Newspapers
          - Correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box 78)
          - Dust jacket, 1981 (Box 78)
          - Permissions requests, 1979-1988 (Box 78)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1981 (Box 78)
          - Spanish edition, 1984-1985 (Box 78)
        - 1984, Strategy in Advertising, 2nd edition
          - Correspondence, 1981-1992 (Box 78)
          - Foreign rights, 1984 (Box 78)
          - Permissions requests, 1983 (Box 78)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1984-1989 (Box 78)
        - 1985, Polls and the Awareness of Public Opinion (Communications Series)
          - Correspondence, 1972-1987 (Box 78)
          - Reviews, 1985 (Box 78)
          - Revision materials, 1946-1988 and undated, 1 of 5 folders (Box 78)
          - Revision materials (continued), 1946-1988 and undated, 2-5 of 5 folders (Box 79)
        - 1989, Press and Public: Who Reads What, When, Where and Why in American Newspapers, 2nd edition (Box 79)
        - 1991, Preserving the Press: How Daily Newspapers Mobilized to Keep Their Readers
          - Background materials, 1966-1994 and undated, 3 folders (Box 79)
          - Correspondence and reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 79)
          - Manuscript draft, circa 1989, 1-2 of 8 folders (Box 79)
          - Manuscript draft (continued), circa 1989, 3-8 of 8 folders (Box 80)
        - 1992, Project Clear: Social Research and the Desegregation of the United States Army
          - Dust jacket, 1992 (Box 80)
          - Revision materials and reviews, 1969-1992 (Box 80)
        - 1995, Cool Words, Cold War: A New Look at USIA's Premises for Propaganda
          - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 80)
          - Research materials, 1993-1997 (Box 80)
          - Reviews and publicity, 1995 (Box 80)
          - USIA clippings,1994-1995 (Box 80)
        - 1995, Commercial Culture: The Media System and the Public Interest
          - Abstract and chapter outline, 1989-1990 (Box 80)
          - Background materials (Box 81)
            - I. Commercialization of Communication, 1965-1995 (Box 81)
            - II. Elite and Commercial Culture, 1973-1989 and undated (Box 81)
            - III. The Content of Commercial Culture, 1965-1995 and undated, 6 folders (Box 81)
            - IV. Commercial Communication, 1966-1989, 4 folders (Box 81)
            - V. Control of Media Content, 1972-1989 and undated, 2 folders (Box 81)
            - V. Control of Media Content, 1972-1989 and undated (Box 82)
            - VI. Triumphs and Tragedies of Commercial Culture, 1970-1989 and undated (Box 82)
            - VII. Fulfilling the Potential, 1970-1989 and undated, 2 folders (Box 82)
            - Arbitron, 1989-1990 (Box 82)
            - General, 1973-1989, 1 of 3 folders (Box 82)
            - General (continued), 1973-1989, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box 83)
          - Book proposal, 1992 (Box 83)
          - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 83)
          - Early Commercial Culture writing, 1986 (Box 83)
          - Early drafts, circa 1975-1985, 1-7 of 12 folders (Box 83)
          - Early drafts (continued), circa 1975-1985, 8-12 of 12 folders (Box 84)
          - Hardcover book, 1995 (Box 84)
          - Interviews, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
          - Notes
            - Chapter notes, circa 1990, 1-3 of 8 folders (Box 84)
            - Chapter notes (continued), circa 1990, 4-8 of 8 folders (Box 85)
            - Early notes, 1968-1986 and undated (Box 85)
            - General, circa 1990, 5 folders (Box 85)
            - Mass media research, 1969-1974, 1 of 2 folders (Box 85)
            - Mass media research (continued), 1969-1974, 2 of 2 folders (Box 86)
          - Reviews, 1994-1997 (Box 86)
          - Transaction edition, 1998-2000 (Box 86)
        - 2003, Finding Out: Personal Adventures in Social Research -- Discovering What People Think, Say, and Do
          - Correspondence and reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 86)
        - 2003, How I Earned the Ruptured Duck: Behind the Lines in WWII
          - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 86)
          - Manuscript draft, 2001, 3 folders (Box 86)
        - 2005, Over the Edge: How the Pursuit of Youth by Marketers and the Media Has Changed American Culture
          - Manuscript draft, circa 2005 (Box 86)
          - Notes, 2003 (Box 86)
        - 2005, American Newspapers: How They Have Changed and How They Must Keep Changing
          - Publisher proofs, 2005 (Box 86)
      - Book Chapters and Contributions
        - 1960, Introduction to A Factor Analytic Study of Attitudes Toward the Mass Media (Box 86)
        - 1964, Mass Media and the Blue-Collar Worker, in Blue-Collar World (Box 86)
        - 1967, Mass Communication -- Audiences, in International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (Box 87)
        - 1968, The Peril of Political Polls, in World Book Encyclopedia Science Service (Box 87)
        - 1968, Social Sciences in the Mass Media in Behavioral Sciences and the Mass Media (Box 87)
        - 1971, Television in Dictionary of Psychology (Box 87)
        - 1972, Where Does Advertising Go From Here? in Frontiers of Advertising Theory and Research (hardcover book) (Box 87)
        - 1973, Consumer and Advertising Research in Handbook on Communication (Box 87)
        - 1974, The Management of Mass Media in Mass Communication Research: Major Issues and Future Directions (Box 87)
        - 1979, Editorial Ideals, Editorial Illusions in The Waning of the Fourth Estate (Box 87)
        - 1980, After the Surgeon General's Report: Another Backward Look in Television and Social Science Behavior: Beyond Violence (Box 87)
        - 1980, Television News as Entertainment in The Entertainment Functions of TV, 2 folders (Box 87)
        - 1983, Mass Media: Knowledge as Entertainment in The Optimum Utilization of Knowledge (Box 87)
        - 1984, Introduction to Update to the Surgeon General's Report on Television and Behavior (Box 87)
        - 1985, Media and a Changing America in Impact of Mass Media (Box 87)
        - 1987, The Return of Hollywood's Mass Audience in Surveying Social Life (Box 87)
        - 1988, Advertising in International Encyclopedia of Communications, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - 1989, Marketing in the Year 2000 in Marketing 2000 (Box 88)
        - 1989, Mass Communication and World Opinion in Political Culture and Public Opinion (Box 88)
        - 1989, Newspapers in Transition in American Media: The Wilson Quarterly Reader (Box 88)
        - 1996, American Communication Research: the Remembered History table of contents (Box 88)
        - 1998, The Turbulent Depths of Marketing in How Advertising Works: The Role of Research (Box 88)
      - Copyright certificates and correspondence, 1969-1983 (Box 88)
      - Publishing contracts, permissions, and requests, 1968-1977 (Box 88)
      - Unpublished writings and drafts
        - circa 1953, On the Reading of Newspaper Comic Strips (Box 88)
        - circa 1955, The Individual and the Crisis Situation (Box 88)
        - 1956, American Beauties: A Footnote on the Cold War (Box 88)
        - 1963, Notes From the USSR (Box 88)
        - 1963, Public Opinion and the Day's News: Reactions to the TV Quiz Hearings (Box 88)
        - 1964, What Marketers Must Know About Advertising Media Strategy (Box 88)
        - circa 1965, International View draft (Box 88)
        - 1968, Big Social Science (Box 88)
        - 1970, The Role of the Private Sector in Social Research (Box 88)
        - circa 1970, comments on Feedback by Leo Bogart (Box 88)
        - circa 1970, Prospects and Problems of Consumer Behavior Research (Box 88)
        - circa 1971, The Negro and the Media (Box 88)
        - 1975, Program Decision-Making for Television (Box 88)
        - 1975 and undated, Some Directions for Study of Media and Presidential Candidates (Box 88)
        - circa 1977, How is 'Advertising Effectiveness' Defined in Practice? (Box 88)
        - 1977-1979, Chapter for The Waning of the Fourth Estate (Box 88)
        - 1981, The Consumer as a Moving Target (Box 88)
        - 1983, Toward a National Media Policy (Box 88)
        - 1984, Introduction (Box 89)
        - 1984-1988, background materials for International Communication and Change by Frederick Yu (Box 89)
        - 1985, The Turbulent Depths of Marketing (Box 89)
        - circa 1985, Marketers Look Ahead (Box 89)
        - 1989, How Inserts and Special Sections are Changing the American Press (Box 89)
        - 1994, The End of Propaganda? (Box 89)
        - 1994, How Should America Talk to the World? (Box 89)
        - 1997, Remote Observers: The Response of Jews in the United States to the European Jewish Catastrophe (Box 89)
        - circa 2000, Courage (Box 89)
        - 2000-2002, Putting Social Research to Work (Box 89)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1956-1998 and undated, miscellaneous drafts and proposals (Box 89)
        - circa 1965-1989, miscellaneous notes, 5 folders (Box 89)
- Photographs & Slides Series, 1949-1993 and undated, 4 boxes
  Consists of photographs, slides, and negatives that document Bogart's personal and professional life. Photographs chiefly document professional meetings and conferences. Slides, which make up the bulk of this series, include Newspaper Advertising Bureau presentation slides; Freedom Forum Russia workshop slides; and family vacation and travel slides. Arranged chronologically.
  - Photographs (Box 90)
    - Personal, circa 1937-1972 (Box 90)
    - Professional
      - circa 1955, Bogart portrait proofs (Box 90)
      - 1961-1979 and undated, Miscellaneous conference photographs (Box 90)
      - 1967, Portland Ad Club (Box 90)
      - circa 1968, AAPOR (Box 90)
      - 1970, Helsinki, Finland (Box 90)
      - 1970, Waldorf Astoria dinner (Box 90)
      - circa 1975, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Box 90)
      - 1977, Atlanta Journal/Atlanta Constitution newspapers meeting (Box 90)
      - 1977, Newspaper Publishers Association of New Zealand luncheon (Box 90)
      - 1977-1985, Preserving the Press photographs (Box 90)
      - 1980, Information Day in Lyon, France (Box 90)
      - 1982, Sao Paulo, Brazil seminar (Box 90)
      - 1983, NRMA speech (Box 90)
      - 1985, Copley Newspapers meeting (Box 90)
      - 1986, Las Vegas, Nevada INAME annual dinner (Box 90)
      - 1989, Newspaper Advertising Bureau (Box 90)
      - circa 1989, Bogart portrait proofs (Box 90)
      - 1992-1993, Freedom Forum Russia workshop trip (Box 90)
  - Negatives
    - 1952, Michele and Leo Bogart (Box 90)
    - Undated, Rome (Box 90)
  - Slides
    - Professional
      - Newspaper Advertising Bureau presentations
        - circa 1980s, Health Care National Show (Box 90)
        - circa 1985, Retail Co-Op Recovery (Box 90)
        - circa 1985-1987, The Search: Advertising Performance and the Reading Process (Box 90)
        - circa 1985-1989, The Classified Connection (Box 90)
        - circa 1985-1989, Do It In Color (Box 90)
        - circa 1985-1989, Great Newspapers (Box 90)
        - circa 1985-1989, The Future of Advertising (Box 90)
        - 1986, The Big Change in Television (Box 90)
        - 1988, Why Newspapers? (Box 90)
      - Freedom Forum Russia workshop, 1992 (Box 91)
        Presentations scripts are in English and Russian and slide text is in Russian. Workshop scripts and correspondence are located in the Freedom Forum Subseries and photographs of the trip are located in the Photographs and Slides Series.
        - I. Why Newspaper Advertising? by Leo Bogart (Box 91)
        - II. The Newspaper Advertising Department by Norman Kirk, 2 folders (Box 91)
        - III. Creating Effective Newspaper Advertising by Bill Solch, 2 folders (Box 91)
        - IV. Taking the Customer's Point of View by Leo Bogart (Box 91)
        - VI. Selling Newspaper Advertising by Bill Solch (Box 91)
        - V. Facing the Competition by Norman Kirk (Box 91)
        - Miscellaneous workshop presentation slides (Box 91)
      - Other presentations (Box 92)
        - circa 1990, Advertising and technology presentation (Box 92)
        - Unidentified, undated (Box 92)
    - Personal
      - 1949-1981, unidentified and miscellaneous travel, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - 1950, Corpus Christi, Texas and New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 92)
      - 1950 and 1958, Virginia (Box 92)
      - 1950-1970, Miscellaneous (Box 92)
      - 1951-1957, Tuscon, Arizona Rodeo Parade (Box 92)
      - 1958-1968, Greg and Michele Bogart (Box 92)
      - 1958, Mexico and Peru (Box 92)
      - 1958-1971, Italy (Box 92)
      - 1960, Southwestern United States (Box 92)
      - 1960, Disneyland (Box 92)
      - 1961, Caribbean (Box 92)
      - 1961, Damascus, Syria; Cyprus; and Greece (Box 92)
      - 1962, Jalisco, Mexico (Box 92)
      - 1962-1963, Martha's Vineyard, St. Simeon, and southwestern United States (Box 92)
      - 1963, Grand Canyon (Box 92)
      - 1963, Russia (Box 93)
      - 1964, Portugal and Spain (Box 93)
      - 1965, Russia (Box 93)
      - 1966, Caribbean (Box 93)
      - 1966, Leo Bogart's Parents (Box 93)
      - 1968, Victoria Falls, Africa (Box 93)
      - 1968, New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 93)
      - 1970, South Africa (Box 93)
      - 1970, West Africa, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - 1971, California (Box 93)
      - 1976, France (Box 93)
      - 1979, Algeria and Tunisia (Box 93)
      - 1979, The Alps and Sardinia (Box 93)
      - 1980, China (Box 93)
      - 1981, Michele Bogart's wedding (Box 93)
      - 1982, Portugal and Spain (Box 93)
      - 1990, Managua, Nicaragua and Scotland (Box 93)
      - undated, Rome, Italy (Box 93)
- Artifacts, 1971-1973, 1 boxes
  - AMA award plaque, 1973 (Box 94)
  - Clio and Effie Awards commemorative director's board, 1971 (Box 94)
- Oversize Materials, 1926-1992, 3 boxes
  - Personal Series (Box 95)
    - Other materials
      - Art prints, undated (Box 95)
      - Cartoons, undated (Box 95)
      - Drawing by Michele Bogart, 1962 (Box 95)
      - L'Illustration, no. 4370, 1926 (Box 95)
      - Russian document, 1908 (Box 95)
        [Copy of diploma of Bogart's father, Iakov Abramovich Bugaevskii, conferring a degree in law from the Imperial Russian University in Odessa.]
  - Professional Series (Box 95)
    - Early Career Subseries
      - Standard Oil (New Jersey)
        - Aruba Oil materials, 1946-1950 (Box 95)
        - Radio studies
          - Average audience bar graph, 1947 (Box 95)
    - Newspaper Advertising Bureau Subseries (Box 96)
      - General
        - Correspondence
          - Creative Newspaper Awards
            - Award winners, 1989-1990 (Box 96)
        - Publications
          - Newspaper Advertising Bureau: What It Is, What It Does, 1984 (Box 96)
        - Research
          - Children and young adults
            - The Mini Page packet, 1978 (Box 96)
            - Minneapolis Star Smile Factory packet, 1978 (Box 96)
            - Minneapolis Star-Tribune circulation study, 1973 (Box 96)
      - Major projects (Box 97)
        - Newspaper Readership Project
          - Promotion & Public Relations Committee
            - I Saw It in the Paper film
              - Promotional booklet, circa 1979 (Box 97)
            - National Better Newspaper Contest, 1981 (Box 97)
            - Newspaper in Education
              - Children's special sections, 1979 (Box 97)
          - Publications
            - How to Have Fun and Profit From Reading Newspapers, 1979 (Box 97)
            - Newspaper inserts, 1977-1979 (Box 97)
            - Newspaper Readership Project in the U.K. reports, 1981-1982 (Box 97)
    - Professional Service Subseries
      - Market Research Council, 1964-1987 (Box 97)
    - Research Files Subseries
      - Marketing News: The 1992 Honomichl Business Report on the Marketing Research Industry, 1992 (Box 97)
  - Photographs & Slides Series (Box 97)
    - Photographs
      - Professional
        - circa 1955, Bogart portrait proofs (Box 97)
        - 1970, Waldorf Astoria dinner (Box 97)
  - Professional Series (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Newspaper Advertising Bureau Subseries
      - General
        - Miscellaneous
          - Leo Bogart is a Heavy Viewer poster, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Research Files Subseries
      - The Emerging Landscape Presstime newspaper readership map, 1998 (Oversize-folder 1)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1972-2004 and undated, 1 boxes
  Consists of videocassettes, DVDs, audiocassettes, CDs, and floppy disks, featuring or collected by Bogart. Many of the videocassettes were used for Bogart's work as a mass media expert in two trials, Chandler v. Jackson (Michael Jackson child molestation lawsuit) and Valenzuela v. Hughes Aircraft Company (TCE groundwater contamination lawsuit in Tuscon, Arizona).
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restrictions on access: Originals are closed to researchers. Contact Research Services for information on obtaining use copies.
  - Original recordings (CLOSED)
    - Video (Box 98)
      - OR1. The Open Mind. Host: Richard Heffner, Guest: Leo Bogart. Show title: The Public Interest Versus the Public's Interests, 2003, Mar. 12. Format: VHS (Box 98)
      - OR2-OR13. Tuscon TCE Coverage, tapes 1-12, 1985-1990. Format: VHS (Box 98)
      - Michael Jackson media coverage clips
        - OR14. Press Conference, undated. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR15. American Justice, undated. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR16. Michael Jackson Changes History, 1995, July 28. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR17. Nightline, 1999, Jan. 25. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR18. A Current Affair, 1998, Nov. 2. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR19. Oprah, 1997, Feb. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR20. Hard Copy, 1994, May 9. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR21-OR23. Hard Copy, undated. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR24. Late Show with David Letterman, undated. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR25. Michael Jackson VH1 interview, 1996, Nov. 10. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR26. News Stories, 1994, Mar. 18. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR27. Maury Povich, 1994, Feb. 21. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR28. Hard Copy, 1994, Jan. 10-11. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR29. Geraldo, 1994, Mar. 2. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR30. Hard Copy, 1994, Feb. 22-24. Format: VHS (Box 98)
        - OR31. An Interview with Leo Bogart. Interviwer: John Carey, Fordham Business School, 2005, Apr. 21. Format: DVD (Box 98)
    - Audio
      - OR32. Berlin, undated. Format: CD (Box 98)
      - OR33. Columbia University seminar on social priorities speech, 1972 Apr. 19. Format: audiocassette (Box 98)
    - Computer files
      - OR34. Untitled, undated. Format: floppy disk (90mm) (Box 98)
      - Freedom Forum Russia workshop